Now something that I often do is I actually hate running yarn hard hat all the time,
实际上，有一件我经常要做但我又很不喜欢做的事，那就是我要一直运行 `yarn hardhat`
because that's too many keys for my little brain to work with.
因为对我这个小脑袋来说，命令实在太多了
I would prefer to write as little keys as possible
我希望写的时候命令尽可能可以少一些
So hard hat comes with a shorthand and autocomplete
因此 Hardhat 提供了“缩写”("Shorthand")和“自动完成”("autocomplete")的功能
hard hat shorthand is an NPM package that installs a globally accessible binary called H H,
"hardhat-shorthand" 是一个 NPM 包，它安装了一个全局可用的二进制文件，名为 "hh"
that runs the project's locally installed hard hat and supports shell auto completion for tasks.
用于运行项目本地安装的 "hardhat" 并支持 shell 自动完成任务
So what we can do is we're going to start with NPM, like this,
我们可以像这样用 npm 进行安装
but we're gonna install it with yarn, we're going to run yarn, global, add hardhat shorthand.
但我们用 yarn 安装，运行 `yarn global add hardhat-shorthand`
And what this is going to do, we can see here installed hard hat shorthand with binaries H, H, and Hardhead completion.
结果怎么样呢？我们可以看这里，"hardhat-shorthand" 二进制文件安装完成，还有 "hh" 以及 "hardhat-completion "
("Installed "hardhat-shorthand" with binaries")
Now instead of running yarn, Hardhead compile, which we can still run, we can just run h h compile,
现在就不需要运行 `yarn hardhat compile` 而是可以运行 `hh compile` 了
running h h is going to be the same thing as if we had just run the Hardhead command for our local directory.
运行 "hh" 就相当于在本地目录运行 "hardhat" 命令